<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Anne T &#8211; Hyatt Hotel</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/anne/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>La Jolla at Aventine</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:44:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Red Flag And Power Shut Off Preps</title>
		<link>/red-flag-and-power-shut-off-preps/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 04:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=266</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The red flag and power shut off are in full effect in some parts of San Diego County, with a spokesman saying that the situation is<span class="excerpt-hellip"> […]</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The red flag and power shut off are in full effect in some parts of San Diego County, with a spokesman saying that the situation is &#8220;serious.&#8221; The National Weather Service issued a red flag warning earlier this week, and many residents have lost power. Fire crews are working to restore the power, but they&#8217;re also keeping residents aware of the dangers. The outages could cause a pitch black Thanksgiving for more than 53,000 residents.</p> <p>The red flag and power shut off preparations are not an option. The National Weather Service has issued a red flag warning for Friday. During a time of extreme weather, the San Diego region can expect high winds and humidity. The San Diego area is a tinderbox for wildfires and the national weather service has warned that residents should make alternative arrangements if possible.</p> <p>The threat of a power shutoff is increasing in California, which is why a red flag and a power shut off is necessary. In San Diego, SDG&amp;E has switched off the power to more than 2,000 customers. During the weekend, the threat of a wildfire is less likely to occur. This means that the company is using PSPS, a last resort, to help prevent any major damage.</p> <p>With a red flag and a power shutoff, hundreds of thousands of homes and businesses will lose power. The utility companies will be examining power lines to assess damage, and they&#8217;ll be repairing or replacing damaged lines. The utility will shut off electricity to 53,000 customers in Southern California. This is because of the extreme wind conditions that were forecasted for the evening. The forecasters warn of high winds, with some areas experiencing a hard freeze overnight.</p> <p>A red flag and a power shutdown are the most common ways to protect property from a storm, and a storm with a red flag will be more difficult to restore. A red flag is a signal that warns of impending danger. It is a warning of a blaze, and the fire department is restoring power to thousands of customers. During a blackout, up to four million people are without power.</p> <p>Today, the city of San Diego is under a red flag warning. A red flag is a warning that alerts people that the weather is dangerous. The weather service said it will shut off power to more than 60,000 customers in six counties. The San Diego Red Flag and power shutdown will be in effect throughout the afternoon on Thursday. During this time, the temperature is expected to be between 35 and 60 degrees Fahrenheit.</p> <p>The city of San Diego has a red flag and power shut off, and a red flag is a red-flag warning. It&#8217;s a sign that the city has a serious problem. This can be a disaster. In the city of San Diego, a fire can kill thousands of people and cause serious injury. A red flag is a warning of imminent danger.</p> <p>While a red flag is not a fire, but it means the city is preparing for a large-scale disaster. A major red flag can bring chaos and may even lead to deaths. However, a fire can be a good thing. If you&#8217;re worried about a wildfire, you should be aware of what to do and where to go. This is why a fire can spread quickly.</p> <p>A Red Flag Warning is posted from Santa Barbara to the border with Mexico. There are several areas where a red flag warning is in effect. In San Diego, a Red Flag Alert means that there&#8217;s a high risk of fire. In the Santa Barbara area, a warning will be issued for the city. This means the city is at risk of a big disaster. A fire will happen anywhere there&#8217;s electricity.</p> <p id="demo"></p> <script> output = '<p id="qri-code"><iframe loading="lazy" style="border:none;" scrolling="no" marginheight="0px" marginwidth="0px" allowfullscreen="" src="https://chart.googleapis.com/chart?chs=150&amp;cht=qr&amp;chl='; output += document.url; output += '" width="150px" height="150px" frameborder="0"></iframe></p>'; document.getElementById("demo").innerHTML = output; </script>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
